我要点咖啡外带 洋娃娃，你也要吗？
I'll get coffee. Want anything,baby doll?
不用了，谢谢
I'm fine. Thanks.
我不能叫你洋娃娃吧
I can't pull off "baby doll," can l?
对，从那次甜甜嘴事件 我们已经得到教训了
No,I think we learned that from the "sugar lips" incident.
我去点茶来喝
I'll make some tea.
小南瓜，你好吗？
How you doing,pumpkin?
不
Nope
你们俩看起来越来越好了呢
-So it's going well for you two?
我知道，真的很好 其实我正想要菲比搬来我家
-I know. Really well.I'm gonna ask Phoebe to move in with me.
天啊
Oh my god！
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
我觉得这真是太棒了 你何时要问她？
It's great! When will you ask her?
今天晚上，你先别透露喔
Tonight. But don't say anything.
我发誓不说，人格担保…
I swear. I promise.
天啊，我超兴奋的
I'm so excited!
我跟你说，记得不要送她花
But listen,do not get her flowers,okay?
因为花谢了她会哭 还会帮花办葬礼之类的
Because she cries when they die. Then there's the whole funeral.
亲爱的，下班后再见 好，再见
-I'll see you after work,sweetie. -Okay. Bye.
我们应该去看什么电影？
So,what movie should we see?
盖瑞要请你搬去跟他住
Gary's gonna ask you to move in with him!
什么？真的吗？
What? Really?
他刚才在吧台上跟我说的
He just told me at the counter
他要我保证不会说出去 但我实在是憋不住
He made me promise not to tell,but I couldn't hold it in any longer!
我不敢相信
I can't believe this.
对，因为太快了，太快…
Right? Because it's fast. Because it's so fast. It's fast.
别激动，是菲比，又不是你
Relax. It's Phoebe,not you.
菲比，很厉害，有一套
Good for you,Phoebe. Way to go.
不过真的是很快，对吧？
No,but it is fast,isn't it?
我是很喜欢他没错 但我还没有准备好
-I like him,but I'm not ready.
那你打算怎么办？
-So,what are you gonna do?
不知道，我会处理的
I don't know. I'll just handle it.
你去跟他谈！
I'll ask you to talk to him!
我？为何是我？
Me? Why me?
因为你怕承诺
Because you are so afraid of commitment.
你去跟他说说 让他跟你一样怕
You talk to him. Make him scared like you,
让他成为一个…男人
make him a man.
我会去试试 但我不确定会多有用
I'll try,but I'm not sure what good it'd do.
因为比起以前 我现在已经不害怕承诺了
I'm less afraid of commitment than I used to be.
真是太甜蜜了
That is so sweet.
还是很怕 但我会处理，没问题
Still terrified. I'll take care of it.No problem
本集播出：“掷球游戏”
The One With the Ball
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
罗斯，斯塔顿岛真的是岛吗？
Hey,Ross,is Staten lsland really an island?
是啊，所以才叫斯塔顿“岛”
That's why they call it Staten "lsland."
我还以为那跟长岛一样
Oh,I thought it was like Long lsland.
长岛也是岛
Also an island.
几点了？
-What time is it?
2点17分
-2:17.
你相信吗？我们丢这个球
Wow！You realize that we've been throwing this ball,
连续一小时都没有落地
without dropping it,for like an hour?
真的吗？
Are you serious?
对，我半小时前就发现了 我怕坏了好事才没说
I realized it a half-hour ago,but I didn't say anything.I didn't wanna jinx it.
我们还真会丢球呢
We are pretty good at this.
我们完全忘了吃午餐
We totally forgot about lunch.
这是我第一次忘记吃饭
That's the first time I've ever missed a meal.
我觉得我的裤子都有点松了
I think my pants are a little loose.
嗨，莫妮卡在吗？
Hey,you guys. Is Monica here?
不在…
No
我买了点东西 我不确定她是否喜欢
I bought something. I'm not sure she'll like it.
听起来有点傻
It may seem crazy,
那个东西我从小就想要了
but I've wanted this since I was a little girl.
你买的是肖恩·卡西迪？ （演员、导演、编剧）
You bought Shaun Cassidy!
不是，我也希望是
No. I wish!
你们准备好了没？ 好了
Okay,you ready?  Yes
请看！
Check it out.
那是什么？ 是什么鬼东西？
What is it?What the hell is that?
这是猫啊
It's a cat.
这才不是猫
That is not a cat!
这就是猫啊
Yes,it is!
它的皮怎么翻出来了？
Why is it inside out?
帮帮忙
Excuse me!
这可是展示级的 纯种斯芬克斯猫
But this is a purebred,show-quality sphinx cat.
你花了多少钱买的？
How much did you pay for that?
有点奢侈 但我谈到了很好的价钱
It was extravagant,but I got a good deal.
是吗？多少钱？
-How much?
一千美元
-Thousand bucks.
买一只猫？
On a cat?
那才不是猫！
It's not a cat!
花一千元起码也要有毛才对
For a thousand dollars,you'd think at least it'd come with hair.
或是其他什么
Or something.
你们这两个玩球的给我听好
All right. Listen,ball boys.
我小时候祖母就养了这种猫 它们最讨人喜欢了
My grandma had one when I was little. It was the sweetest thing.
超可爱的，躺在我的膝盖上 整天满足地喵喵叫
It would sit in my lap and just purr all day long.
我还会拿鞋带在地上拖 让它追着跑
I would drag a string and it would chase it.
不要钱的猫也会那样
Free cats do that too,you know.
那才不是猫！
It's not a cat!
反正我很兴奋 我才不管你们怎么想
I'm really excited about this,okay? I don't care what you think.
我要去给威丝克森太太准备一个小盒子
I'm gonna set up a litter box for Mrs. Whiskerson.
不然我要叫它“毛毛”吗？
What am I gonna call her? Fluffy?
你要去吃点东西吗？
Do you wanna get something to eat,
还是要看我们能来回丢多久？
or see how long we can throw this ball?
继续丢球 是喔
The ball thing.
若我们连丢两小时不落地 那样是不是很棒？
Wouldn't it be great if we could go for two hours without dropping it?
对喔
Yeah,it would!
来吧 好
Let's do it.
怎么了？
What？
我要尿尿，瑞秋在厕所里
I have to pee.And Rachel's in the bathroom!
没想到这样也行
Man,I didn't think we'd make it.
是啊
I know.
不要换手，好吗
Don't switch hands,okay?
小姐们，你们在这里干嘛？
Hey,ladies. What are you in here for?
钱德，你来这里干嘛？
What are you doing here?
盖瑞，我是来报案的 是吗？
I am here to report a crime.
我们俩不常聚在一起 是一种罪
It's a crime that we don't spend time together.
你有什么事？
What's up?
听说你在考虑要菲比跟你同居
You're thinking about moving in with Phoebe,
我心想我们或许应该聊聊 男人…跟我的对话
and I thought we should talk.You know,man to...well,me.
好啊，没问题
Sure,okay.
你疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
你疯了？若你和菲比同居 你们两个就会住在一起了
Are you insane?If you live with Phoebe,you two are gonna be living together.
对，我考虑过了 我知道这会让我快乐
I considered that. It'd make me happy.
你是说害怕吧
-You mean scared.
不，我是说快乐
-No,I mean happy.
恐怖的快乐？
Scared happy.
钱德，你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
我在让你张开眼睛啊 你看不出来吗？
I'm trying to open your eyes! Don't you see
若你和菲比同居 她就永远都会在
If you live with Phoebe,she is always gonna be there.
你回家会看到她 你上床也会看到她
You get home,she's there. You go to bed,she's there.
你起床呢？对，她还是在
You wake up and,oh,yes,she's there.
我知道，我都等不及了
I know. I can't wait!
你父母的婚姻很幸福吧？
Were your parents happy or something?
钱德，我看这件事的角度是 我很幸运能找到我的真爱
I was lucky enough to find someone that I really love.
我想要尽量多跟她在一起
I just want to be around her as much as I can.
这件事从你嘴里说出来 感觉就没那么恐怖了
When you say it,it doesn't sound so scary.
所以你懂我的意思吧？ 对，我想我懂
You know what I'm saying?Yeah,I think I do.
知道吗，跟她同居吧
You know what?Move in with her.
马上就去跟她同居
Move in right now.
或许我也应该和莫妮卡同居
Maybe I'll move in with Monica.
不成，你们不能操之过及
No,it's too soon for you guys.
是啊，你说的对
You're right about that.
他们找到中生代乳齿象化石
When they found the remains of the Mesozoic mastodon...
却在嘴部发现到 类似古生代两栖类的构造
...they discovered what appeared to be the remains of a Paleozoic amphibian in its jaws.
它们从哪里冒出来的？
How did it get there?
或许这个游戏应该安静一点
Maybe this should be more of a quiet game.
嗨 嗨
Hey,guys.
我昨晚把手表放在柜子上
I left my watch here last night.
应该在这里的，到哪儿去了？
-lt was here. Where is it?
我不知道
-I don't know.
别闹了，我上班快迟到了
Come on，I'm late for work.
你怎么知道？你又没戴表
How do you know? You don't have a watch.
能不能停一下再丢球 先帮我找表？
Can you stop throwing the ball for one minute and help me find it?
不知道，没办法喔
Oh,I don't know.... Yeah,can't do it.
怎样啦？
-What?
莫妮卡，怎样都好 千万别把球掉地上
-Monica，whatever you do，do not drop that ball.
我们保持球不落地已经…
We haven't dropped it in....
2小时27分钟
Two hours,27 minutes.
真的啊？
Really?
我今天没办法去上班 我人不太舒服
I won't make it in to work today.I don't feel very good.
漂亮！
Yes
我刚才突然觉得自己好多了 但其实没有
For a second,I thought I was feeling better,but I'm not.
瑞秋 嗨
Hey,Rach.
快来看，球不落地接近三小时
Check it out. Almost three hours without dropping it.
恭喜了，真是浪费时间的好办法
Congratulations. That's quite a waste of time.
瑞秋？ 怎么了？
Rach？Yeah？
你身上都是抓痕，怎么了？
You have scratches all over you.What happened？
是我的猫 什么？
Well,it's my cat. What？
对了，我养了一只猫
-Oh,I got a cat.
我不想养猫
-I don't want a cat!
别担心，那不是猫 没错
Don't worry,it's not a cat.  Yeah
这只猫跟我祖母养过的猫 完全不一样
You guys,this cat is nothing like my grandmother's cat.
既不讨人喜欢，也不可爱
It's not sweet. It's not cute.
我拉着线逗它
I dragged a string,
它竟然发飙 把我抓得乱七八糟
and it flipped out and scratched the hell out of me.
我知道这听来很疯狂 但
I know this sounds crazy,
这只猫每次嘘我的时候 我知道它都在说“瑞秋”
but every time this cat hisses at me I know it's saying,"Rachel!"
花一千美元买一只猫 比刚才那些话更疯狂
Doesn't sound as crazy as paying $1000 for a cat.
你欠我三百美元不还 还拿一千美元去买猫？
You paid $1000 for a cat when you owe me $300?
我本来打算让你跟它玩的
Well,I was gonna let you play with it.
“中央咖啡馆”
嗨
Hi
你跟盖瑞聊过同居的事没？
Did you talk to Gary about moving in?
聊过了，我觉得你应该答应
I think you should do it.
什么？
What？
他很棒，他也很爱你 你非常幸运
He's a great guy and he loves you a lot. You are a very lucky lady.
你真没用
You are useless!
害怕承诺是你唯一会做的事
Freaking out about commitment is the one thing you can do...
你竟然连那件事都做不好！ 天啊
...and you can't even do that right!
抱歉
Sorry.
如果他问我，我也愿意和他同居
If he asked me,I'd move in with him.
天啊
God！
没用的家伙，快滚吧
Get out of here,good-for-nothing.
钱德 盖瑞
Hey,Chandler.Hey,Gar.
亲爱的
Hey,sweetie.
能不能先聊一下？ 好啊
Can I talk to you for a second?
你今天很美
You look pretty today.
谢谢，好吧
Thanks. Okay.
是这样的
Here's the thing.
我很想让这段关系更进一步
I really want this relationship to move forward.
因为不进则退
If you're not moving forward,you're moving backwards.
不对，那不是真的 如果不进，就是静止不动
No,if you're not moving forward,you're staying still.
静止不动是很好的，你看
And staying still is good. Watch this.
菲比 是
Phoebe？ Yes
我要你搬来一起住
I want you to move in with me.
那真是太甜蜜了
That is so sweet.
但你不觉得太快了些吗？
But don't you think it's too soon?
我们彼此还有太多地方不了解
There's so much we don't know about each other.
好吧，我懂了
Okay. I get it.
我只是不希望我们操之过急 你懂吧？
I don't want us to jump into something that we're not ready for.
我不想搞砸我们现在的一切
I don't want to mess up what we have.
我担心同居会铸成大错
I'm worried it's gonna be a big mistake.
是啊
Ya
所以我的答案是我答应
Which is why my answer is yes!
真的吗？
Really?
我好快乐
You're so happy.
莫妮卡，别丢那么大力！
Monica,stop throwing it so hard!
我们是同一队
We're on the same team!
四个小时？ 你们就这样丢了四小时？
You guys have been doing this for four hours?
宝贝，没错
That's right,baby.
好，让我加入
-All right. Let me in.
不行！…
-No,no! Don't do it!
什么？
What?
他是掉球大王
He's a dropper.
对，没错！
Oh,yeah. That's right!
我才不是掉球大王
I'm not a dropper!
这其实是三个人的游戏
It's really a three-person game,you know?
还不就是你丢我接
It's throwing and catching.
好吧
All right.
好难喔
Oh,it's so hard.
别紧张，那不是猫喔
Don't worry,guys. It's not a cat.
我的…天啊
Oh,good God!
我放弃了 我不知道要怎么处理
I give up. I don't know what I'm gonna do with this thing.
送它进烤箱也没用？
Baking it didn't help?
把它送回你买的地方呢？
Take it back to where you got it.
我试过了，他们不收
I tried. They won't take her back.
或许是因为它是反基督的
Maybe that's because she's a minion of the Antichrist.
瑞秋，店家为什么不收？
Why won't they take it?
他们说要收回可以 但只退我店里的购物券
They said they would only give me store credit.
我要拿来买什么？ 一千只普通的猫？
What am I gonna do? Get 1000 regular cats?
你不是说这是展示猫吗？ 那就带去比赛拿奖品啊
You said it was a show cat. Why don't you show it,win some prize money.
参加猫展要先缴一百美元
Those shows cost a hundred bucks to enter,...
赢来的东西都归这死猫所有
and all you win are these ribbons which technically belong to the damn cat.
你先留着 直到你找到处理的方法
You can keep it until you find out what to do with it.
不行，那不是重点
That's not the point.
我破费一千美元 搞得全身都是抓痕
I'm out $1000...I'm all scratched up
还跟长得像手的蠢猫困在一起
...and I'm stuck with this stupid cat that looks like a hand!
天啊，那只猫害我流眼泪了
Oh,my God!The cat's made my eyes water.
别丢球给我！
Don't throw it to me!
我的视力被连累到了
My vision's been compromised!
天啊，好了…
Oh,God! Okay.
现在好了，真是惊险
It's okay. Man,that was close.
是啊，你的反应也太大了点
Yeah,you almost overreacted to something.
我们有个好消息
-We have great news.
我们要同居，是不是很棒？
-We're moving in together. Yay!
恭喜… 是啊，我好兴奋
Congratulations.-I'm so excited!
我也是
-So am l.
你才没有我兴奋，不可能 我是最兴奋的
You're not more excited than I am. No way. I'm the most excited.
好，晚点在局里见
See you at the station later.
好，晚点见 别忘了同居的事喔
I'll see you later. Don't forget about the moving-in!
你要搬去跟他住，怎么了？
So you're moving in with him?
我不忍心拒绝他 看他伤心成那样
I couldn't tell him no. He got so sad.
或许不会有事的
Maybe it'll be all right.
我真的很喜欢他 同居也是迟早的事
I do like him a lot...and probably do it eventually,anyway.
想想也可以省下不少邮票钱
Plus,think of all the money I'll save on stamps.
你常写信给他？
Do you write him a lot?
不是，只是我听说同居的人 会分担邮票的费用，不是吗？
I heard when people live together...they split the cost of stamps,don't they?
是啊，没错…
-Yeah,yeah. -That's right.
抱歉，耐热手套吓了我一跳
Sorry,the oven mitts really freaked me out.
亲爱的
Hey,honey.
你找到公寓没？ 布鲁克林高地有吗？
Did you find any apartments in Brooklyn Heights?
不，没找到
No,nothing.
真的？ 是啊
-Oh,really? -Yeah.
一间都没有？
-Nothing at all? -No.
没有，只要有公寓招租 我们马上搬进去
If something opens up,we'll move in.
如果附带游泳池的话 我需要游泳池
If it has a pool. I need a pool.
菲比，可以跟你聊一下吗？
Can I talk to you?
请坐 好
Take a seat.
你没事吧？还好吧？
You okay?You feel all right?
我很好啊，因为我们要同居了
I feel great,because we're moving in together.
报纸上布鲁克林高地的租屋广告 你都看过了？
So you....You checked the paper for listings in Brooklyn Heights,right?
邮报你有查过吗？
You checked the Post?
是的，什么都没有
Yeah,there was nothing.
我能喝点水吗？ 等会儿
-Can I get some water? -ln a minute.
你查过今天的邮报吗？
You checked today's Post?
对，今天的
Yeah,today's.
这是今天的邮报
Because this is today's Post.
我找到了这些租屋广告
And these are the listings I found.
布鲁克林高地，两房
Brooklyn Heights,two bedrooms.
布鲁克林高地，一房
Brooklyn Heights,one bedroom.
布鲁克林高地区…
Brooklyn Heights,Brooklyn Heights,Brooklyn Heights!
这些是要租的吗？
Oh,are these for rent?
我以为他们是在 炫耀自己的房子有多棒
I thought people were just bragging.
我来告诉你我的想法
Let me tell you what's going on here.
不要看桌子，看着我
Don't look at the table. Look at me.
一个男生要求一个女生同居
Somebody asked someone to move in with him.
女生本来说好，现在反悔了
Someone said yes,but now she has doubts...
因为女生觉得这样太快了
...because things are moving too fast.
你觉得是不是这样？
Does that sound possible?
对！…好，我就是那个女生
Yes,fine! I am someone!
你要我说老实话？ 对，我是不确定
You want me to say it? I have doubts!
对不起
I'm sorry!
菲比？
Phoebe
你有这种感觉也没关系
It's okay that you feel this way.
这真的是很快 我们对彼此有许多地方不了解
It is soon,and there's things we don't know about each other.
我只是觉得 我所了解的你，我很喜欢
Everything I know about you,I really like.
我还不了解的你 就等同居后再慢慢了解
Things I don't know,I'll learn in a place with our names on the mailbox.
好甜蜜
That's so sweet.
亲爱的
Sweetheart
如果你觉得这样太快 没关系
But if it's too soon for you,it's fine
不用赶着现在就同居 我只要你快乐
we don't have to do it.I want you to be happy.
跟你同居会让我快乐的
Living with you would make me happy.
菲比，你不用那样说
You don't have to say that.
不，我很想跟你住在一起 我要跟你同居
I want to live with you. I want to move in with you.
你确定？
Are you sure?
对，百分之百确定！
Definitely,yes!
我们一起住在公寓同居吧
Let's live in an apartment we both live in.
太好了
Oh,that's great.
等等…
Oh,wait,one sec.
镜子后面的人
Hey,you! Behind the glass.
你看什么看？
Who are you looking at?
我经常想在审讯室说这些话
I always wanted to say that every time I was in these rooms,
从未试过呢
which was never.
展示猫，高级的展示猫
Show cat!Quality show cat!
展示猫
-Show cat!
天啊，你的宝宝怎么了？
-Oh,my God!What's wrong with your baby?
这不是宝宝，这是猫
That's not a baby. That's a cat.
长得还真吓人
-It's creepy-looking.
不，它其实很讨人喜欢的… 不信你看
-Oh,no.It's actually very sweet. It's very sweet. Look.
你要不要？
Yeah. Do you want it?
不了，我恨猫
No,I hate cats.
那你干嘛跟我扯半天？ 滚吧，继续走你的路
Then what are you doing to me?Get out of here,all right? Move on!
拜托
Please
这只猫真不寻常
What an unusual cat.
是的，谢谢你 真的是这样，你要吗？
Yes,thank you! Exactly. You want it?
有可能，我考虑要养猫 我正要去流浪动物之家…
Maybe.I was thinking about getting a cat from the shelter,but....
好吧，就它了
-Okay. Why not?
太好了，总共是两千美元
-Oh,terrific! That'll be $2,000.
什么？
-What?
好吧，一千
-Okay,1000.
你不是要我认养你的猫吗？
Didn't you want me to adopt your cat?
是啊，不过这不只是猫 更是一项投资
I do,but you'll have to look at this as more of an investment than a cat.
好吧，我要的只是猫
Okay,yeah. I just wanted a cat.
你显然是杀价高手
Obviously,you know how to haggle,
所以我就不唬弄你了
so I won't try and take you on.
算你八百，我也不报警了 因为你这根本是抢劫
So $800,and I don't call the cops,because you are robbing me blind!
把钱留下，猫带走 走吧…
Blind! Just take the cat. Leave the money. Run away!
可恶！
Run away. Damn it!
死猫，你起码也笑一下嘛
Cat，Can't you at least smile or something?
有没有人听到？谁听到了？
Did anybody just hear that? Anybody?
我饿死了
-I'm starving.
你们振作一点 就快连续十小时了
-Come on,guys. Suck it up!We're closing in on 10 hours.
这是比毅力的时刻
It's gut-check time!
怎么变成是你当老大？ 这游戏是我们发明的
I don't know who made you the boss. We invented this game.
帮帮忙，这游戏是因为我 才有现在的局面
Please，I made this game what it is!
不再好玩的局面？
Not fun anymore?
我还是很饿
I'm still hungry.
好吧，我那还有一点披萨 你们可以用一只手吃吧？
There's pizza at my place. We can eat with one hand.
要不要？ 我要
Are you with me?-I am.
好，我们走…
-All right,let's go! Come on!
莫妮卡大队，走啰
Let's go,Team Monica!
好啦，队名等一下再讨论
We can work out the name later.
瑞秋，你的猫在我碗里干嘛？
What is your cat doing in my bowl?
不是啦，我在解冻鸡肉
I'm defrosting a chicken.
我把威丝克森太太卖掉了
I sold Mrs. Whiskerson.
谢天谢地
Thank God!
你的钱拿回来没？
-Get your money back?
是的，一千五百美元
-Yeah,$1500.
哇，你还有赚耶
You made a profit?
我是来拿红丝绒枕头的
I just came for the red velvet pillow.
在这里 瑞秋，谢了
-There you go. -Thanks,Rachel.
别忘了，你随时可以来看它
Don't forget,you can come visit her anytime.
好…我会记得的
Oh,good. Great. I'll keep that in mind.
这是什么东西？某种蛇吗？
So is this some kind of snake or something?
我真喜欢和你一起醒来 我也是
I like waking up with you.I like waking up with you too.
今天早上真美
Oh,it's such a beautiful morning.
我可以在床上待一整天
I could stay here all day.
那样不错
That would be great.
我们可以在床上吃早餐
-We could have breakfast in bed.
等等 好
-Wait,just a second.
噢，不
Oh,no.
来，莫妮卡，活力点…
All right. Come on,Monica! Look alive. Come on!
罗斯
Ross
我刚才做了最棒的梦 什么梦？
Oh,I was having the best dream.-What?
我梦到自己溺水 不用再丢这颗球了
-I dreamed I was drowning...and not throwing this ball.
很好，你们都起床了
Oh,good. You're all up.
菲比，现在才早上六点 你怎么没在盖瑞那里？
It's 6:00 in the morning. Why aren't you at Gary's?
对，结束了 什么？
Oh,yeah. That's over.What？
别这样，盖瑞这么好 有什么问题都能解决的
Come on，Gary's such a great guy. You can work it out.
他开枪杀了一只鸟 结束了
-He shot a bird. -That is over.
我很遗撼…太糟糕了…
-I'm sorry. -That's terrible.
菲比，你还好吧？
Are you okay?
对…我不会有事的
I'll be all right.
菲比，接住
Here,Phoebe.
我不太想玩球
I don't feel like playing.
没事…
It's okay. It's okay.
就当没发生这件事 没必要让别人知道
It didn't happen. No one needs to know.
菲比又不是正式的队员 正式队员掉球才算数
She's not an official ball player.Only official ball players can drop the ball.
算了…我们走吧…
-Come on. -Let's go.
菲比，要吃早餐吗？ 好啊
You wanna get breakfast?
好，我们来赛跑，最先到的赢
Okay,let's race!First one there wins.
你们要在这里吃吗？ 好啊
You guys wanna eat here? Oh ya！
真的很棒吧？
That was great,huh?
真不敢相信我们丢了那么久
Can you believe how long we threw it?
是啊，撑了那么久 真的很不可思议
It is amazing it lasted that long.
是啊，我的手臂酸死了
My arm is killing me.
不是，我是说有掉球高手在 还能那么久
No,I meant with the dropper over here.
“掉球高手”这称号 怎么会落到我头上？
How did I get this reputation as a dropper?
我再怎么说也不是掉球高手
I am anything but a dropper.
罗斯…
Ross!